https://ernieels.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
At The Els Group we respect the privacy needs of our valued customers and members. This Privacy Policy outlines what specific information is gathered on the Ernie Els site and how that information is used.
Maintaining the privacy of your information is of paramount importance to us as it helps foster confidence, goodwill and stronger relationships with you, our customers. If, at any time, you have questions or concerns about our privacy practices, please feel free contact us.
Information Collection and Use
The Els Group collects information that personally identifies you (“personal information”) in some circumstances, for example when you apply for our services or our customers provide your personal information to us so that we can help them communicate with you by email. The types of personal information we collect include name, contact details and information submitted in forms.
Under no circumstances will The Els Group make any personal information about an individual user available publicly.
Your email address is used to only send you information that you have requested.
The Els Group adheres strictly to permission-based email policy.
The Els Group will not sell, rent, or loan our contact lists or our customer’s contact lists (including customer data) to any outside firms.
All emails that you have requested will have an option to unsubscribe. Unsubscribe requests are fulfilled within minutes and no further communications will be sent to users who have stated that they do not wish to receive the specified information.
We may not be able to do the things described above without your personal information. For example, we may not be able to communicate with you and deal with your enquiries.
Disclosure
The Els Group will not use or disclose your personal information without your consent, except:
where required or authorised by law
to implement the terms of any agreement we have with you
to assist the lawful investigation of a law enforcement authority
the assets and operations of the business are transferred to another party as a going concern; or
as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.
Subscriber Lists, Campaign Content and Campaign Reports
The Els Group employs a range of measures to protect the privacy and confidentiality of personal information in subscriber lists, email content and reports. We use Campaign Monitor to scan the content of your campaigns to protect against defamatory, inaccurate, abusive, obscene, profane, or threatening material that is racially or ethnically offensive.
Communications from the Site
Special Offers and Updates
We send all new users a welcoming email to verify their new account and confirm their password and username. Established users will occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications. Customers can unsubscribe via the unsubscribe mechanism at the bottom of each email.
Newsletter
If a user wishes to subscribe to our newsletter, we ask for contact information such as name and email address. Out of respect for our users privacy we provide a way to opt-out of these communications via the unsubscribe mechanism at the bottom of each email.
Service Announcements
On rare occasions it is necessary to send out a strictly service related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance we might send users an email. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.
Customer Service
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the user’s wishes.
Website Usage Information
We do not link your IP address which accesses our website to any personal information. We use tracking information to determine which areas our site users visit based on traffic to those areas. The Els Group does not track what individual users read, but rather how often each page is visited. This helps us maintain a superior and informative website for you.
Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer’s hard disk for record keeping purposes. Most web browsers are set to accept cookies. The Els Group uses cookies to make your use of our website and services as convenient as possible. Cookies are useful to estimate our number of visitors and to determine overall traffic patterns through our website. If you do not wish to receive any cookies you may set your browser to refuse cookies. This may mean you will not be able to take full advantage of The Els Group’s services.
In some cases third parties may use cookies and other technologies such as web beacons and JavaScript on our website in connection with online services like website analytics and surveys. This may allow them to collect information about your use of our website (including your computer’s IP address) which they may store in the United States or other countries. The use of these technologies allows them to deliver customised evaluate users use of our website and other websites and provide other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Those third parties may also transfer the information they collect to others where required to do so by law, or where those others process the information on their behalf. The services we may use from time to time include Google Analytics, Yahoo, Adobe and Microsoft. You can find more details in the privacy policies for those services, including information on how to opt-out of certain conduct.
Our website may contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or policies of those sites.
Security Technology
The Els Group has made a substantial investment in server, database, backup and firewall technologies to protect our information assets. These technologies are deployed as part of sophisticated security architecture. All data resides in a tightly controlled, secure data center. These investments mean that information about the identity and preferences of individual members is strongly protected by The Els Group against unauthorised access. We will maintain safeguards to protect the security of these servers and your personal information.
Policy Modifications
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If/when The Els Group makes changes to this privacy statement, we will highlight the changes on our homepage and email users who have given us permission to do so. We will post any changes here, so be sure to check back periodically.
Contacting The Els Group about Privacy
If you have any questions about our privacy statement, the information we have collected from you online, the practices of this website, or you wish to access or correct the personal information we hold about you, please email: info@ernieels.com.
In the case of access and correction requests, please provide as much detail as you can about the particular information you seek, in order to help us locate it. We will comply with any applicable legal requirements to provide reasons if we deny any request for access or correction, or to make a requested note of your desired correction with the information.
We take your privacy concerns seriously. Where you express any concerns that we have interfered with your privacy, we will respond to let you know who will be handling your matter and when you can expect a further response.
Sponsors
Partners
-->
Connect
Home
Golf
About Ernie
Weekly Diary
